Y'all, it is my favorite time. It is
time to apply what we just learned. So,
I've got a project here for you. So,
what I want you to do is I want you to
write a bunch of functions. Um, I want
you to write add, subtract, multiply,
divide, modulus, and power. And each of
them should return the result of doing
that mathematical operation between two
numbers. So, they should each take two
numbers. they should then add, subtract,
multiply, divide, uh give the remainder
in the modulus case, raise it to another
power, um all of that. And so that's
what each of those functions should do.
And then I after that, I want you to
write a calculate function that takes
two numbers and one of the above
functions as parameters. And then I want
you to apply the calculation. Call the
calculate function with each one of the
functions previously mentioned and alert
the results. Good luck.